<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="39">
	<author>{package_author}</author>
	<version>{package_version}</version>
	<title>
		<en>Alpego KF7-300</en>
	</title>
	<description>
		<en>
			<![CDATA[Alpego KF7-300 Super Cracker - Subsoiler with optional hydraulic franter roller.

Price: 11000 - 2500 €
working speed: 12 kmh
Required power: 160 - 40 hp
Working width: 3 m
Maintenance: 5 - 3 € / day

Tool with double work option: with franter roller up working in depth as plough function, with franter roller down working on surface, as a cultivator.
Franter rollers are optional and must be purchased separately in the cultivator section.

Changelog {package_version}
- now with separated franter roller buyable as a cultivator
]]>
		</en>
		<de>
			<![CDATA[Alpego KF7-300 Super Cracker - Tiefenlockerer mit optionale hydraulischer Franter-Walze.

Preis: 11000 - 2500 €
Arbeitsgeschwindigkeit: 12 kmh
Benötigte Leistung: 160 - 40 hp
Arbeitsbreite: 3 m
Unterhaltskosten: 5 -3 € / Tag

Dieses Gerät kann sowohl als Grubber, wie auch Pflug genutzt werden. Ist die Rolle oben, ist die Pflugfunktion aktiv - Ist die Rolle unten, dann wirkt der Tiefenlockerer nur als Grubber.
Franter Walzen sind optionale und müssen separat im Grubberbereich gekauft werden.

Changelog {package_version}
- now with separated franter roller buyable as a cultivator
]]>
		</de>
		<fr>
			<![CDATA[Alpego KF7-300 Super Cracker - Décompacteur équipé du double rouleau franter à réglage hydraulique en option.

Price: 11000 - 2500 €
working speed: 12 kmh
Required power: 160 - 40 hp
Working width: 3 m
Maintenance: 5 - 3 € / day

Ce décompacteur a une chance de faire un double-tricot, avec des rouleaux œuvres riches en profondeur avec la fonction de charrue, avec de faibles rouleaux la profondeur de travail est réduite et la fonction est le cultivateur.
Les rouleaux sont facultatifs et doivent être achetés séparément dans la section de cultivateur.

Changelog {package_version}
- now with separated franter roller buyable as a cultivator
]]>
		</fr>
		<it>
			<![CDATA[Alpego KF7-300 Super Cracker - Ripuntatore a 7 ancore con rulli franter idraulici

Prezzo: 11000 - 2500 €
velocità di lavoro: 12 kmh
Potenza richiesta: 160 - 40 hp
Larghezza di lavoro: 3 m
Manutenzione giornaliera: 5 - 3 € / giorno

Questo attrezzo ha la possibilità di effettuare una doppia lavorazione, con i rulli alti lavora in profondità con funzione aratro, con i rulli bassi la profondità di lavoro è ridotta e la funzione è di coltivatore;
i rulli sono opzionali e devono essere acquistati a parte nella sezione coltivatori.

Changelog {package_version}
- now with separated franter roller buyable as a cultivator
]]>
		</it>
	</description>
	<iconFilename>icon.dds</iconFilename>
	<multiplayer supported="true"/>
	<l10n>
		<text name="function_subsoilers">
			<en>A subsoiler can be used to crumble and break up soil in deep.</en>
			<de>Ein Tieflockerer kann verwendet werden, um Boden in der Tiefe zu lösen und aufzubrechen.</de>
			<fr>A décompacteur peut être utilisé pour desserrer et briser le sol en profondeur.</fr>
			<it>Un ripuntatore può essere utilizzato per rompere e sgretolare il terreno in profondità.</it>
		</text>
		<text name="function_techspec">
			<en>Power 160/300 HP - 7 anchors with gradual penetration angle, work width 3000mm, max dteph 650mm, wiegth 1480 kg, optional franter H20 with hydraulical regulation</en>
			<de>Für Traktoren von 160/300 HP - 7 Zinken mit progressivem Anstellwinkel, Arbeitsbreite 3000mm, Tiefe max 650mm, franter-walzen mit hydraulischer Einstellung verfügbar, Gewicht 1480 kg</de>
			<fr>Pour des tracteurs allant de 160 à 300 CH. - 7 Dent avec angle de pénétration progressif, Largeur de travail 3000mm, Profondeur max 650mm, double rouleau franter à réglage hydraulique, poids 1480 kg</fr>
			<it>Potenza richiesta 160/300 CV - 7 ancore - Larghezza di lavorazione 3000mm, Profondità max 650mm, franter H20 con regolazione di profondità idraulica, Peso 1480 kg</it>
		</text>
	</l10n>
	<storeItems>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="alpegoKF7300.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="alpegoFranterH10.xml"/>
	</storeItems>
	<brands>
		<brand name="ALPEGO" title="Alpego" image="brand_alpego.dds"/>
	</brands>
</modDesc>
